<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Hoai Viet Blog</title>
    <link>http://hoaiviet.space/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Hoai Viet Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://hoaiviet.space/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Calabash: Hướng dẫn cách cài đặt để kiểm thử ứng dụng iOS tự động với Calabash</title>
      <link>http://hoaiviet.space/blog/2016/01/17/calabash-h%C6%B0%E1%BB%9Bng-d%E1%BA%ABn-c%C3%A1ch-c%C3%A0i-%C4%91%E1%BA%B7t-%C4%91%E1%BB%83-ki%E1%BB%83m-th%E1%BB%AD-%E1%BB%A9ng-d%E1%BB%A5ng-ios-t%E1%BB%B1-%C4%91%E1%BB%99ng-v%E1%BB%9Bi-calabash/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://hoaiviet.space/blog/2016/01/17/calabash-h%C6%B0%E1%BB%9Bng-d%E1%BA%ABn-c%C3%A1ch-c%C3%A0i-%C4%91%E1%BA%B7t-%C4%91%E1%BB%83-ki%E1%BB%83m-th%E1%BB%AD-%E1%BB%A9ng-d%E1%BB%A5ng-ios-t%E1%BB%B1-%C4%91%E1%BB%99ng-v%E1%BB%9Bi-calabash/</guid>
      <description>Giới thiệu về Calabash http://calaba.sh/
Giới thiệu về Calabash Calabash là một ứng dựng nguồn mở và miễn phí để kiểm thử tự động các ứng dụng di động. Nó là ứng dụng đa nền tảng và hỗ trợ cả iOS và Android. Calabash bao gồm những thư viện cho phép tương tác với các native app và hybrid app giống như người dùng cuối bao gồm các hành động như giả lập cử chỉ, xác định đúng sai và chụp hình màn hình…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CasperJS/PhantomJS - Tutorial</title>
      <link>http://hoaiviet.space/blog/2015/12/29/casperjs/phantomjs---tutorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://hoaiviet.space/blog/2015/12/29/casperjs/phantomjs---tutorial/</guid>
      <description>We use PhantomJS - This acts as browser to run test in. CasperJS - build for PhantomJS, this give you some nice utilities for testing such as clicks and logging events.
Steps 1 - Install Node.js and NPM $ brew install node  Steps 2 - Install PhantomJS $ npm install phantomjs -g  To test that PhantomJS has installed and is accessible through your terminal:
phantomjs -v  This will return version of phantomjs Write your first PhantomJS hello world script.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calabash: Ruby API</title>
      <link>http://hoaiviet.space/blog/2015/12/25/calabash-ruby-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://hoaiviet.space/blog/2015/12/25/calabash-ruby-api/</guid>
      <description>Ruby API When writing custom steps, you&amp;rsquo;ll need to use the Ruby API to interact with your application. This document describes the API at a high level. If you want to see details you can look at the source code in the files at ruby-gem/lib/calabash-android. There are functions in the source code which aren&amp;rsquo;t documented here. Those are way more likely to change (so be warned if you rely on those).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calabash: Calabash-iOS for iOS tutorial</title>
      <link>http://hoaiviet.space/blog/2015/12/23/calabash-calabash-ios-for-ios-tutorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://hoaiviet.space/blog/2015/12/23/calabash-calabash-ios-for-ios-tutorial/</guid>
      <description>Calabash iOS http://calaba.sh/
Calabash is an automated testing technology for Android and iOS native and hybrid applications.
Calabash is a free-to-use open source project that is developed and maintained by Xamarin.
Requirements We recommend that you use the most recent released version of Xcode, MacOS, and Ruby.
 MacOS 10.10 or 10.11 Xcode 6 or 7 iOS Devices &amp;gt;= 7.1 iOS Simulators &amp;gt;= 8.0 ruby &amp;gt;= 2.0 (latest is preferred)  For the best Ruby experience we recommend that you use a managed Ruby like rbenv or rvm).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calabash: Calabash-Android tutorial</title>
      <link>http://hoaiviet.space/blog/2015/12/22/calabash-calabash-android-tutorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://hoaiviet.space/blog/2015/12/22/calabash-calabash-android-tutorial/</guid>
      <description>Automation Testing for Android App Requirement  JAVA JDK ANDROID SDK RUBY
  Install Java JDK Download and install from here: Java JDK
Install and setup Android SDK. Download and install Android SDK for Mac from hereAndroid SDK Stand alone download Download and unzip, then we need to export environment variable ANDROID_HOME and PATH to two folder platform-tools and toolsfrom Android SDK folder
Set ANDROID_HOME by enter commend below to Terminal</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>